תנו לשמש לעלות
Let the sun rise
לבוקר להאיר
Light up the morning
הזכה שבתפילות
The purest of prayers
אותנו לא תחזיר
Will not bring us back
מי אשר כבה נרו
He whose candle was snuffed out
ובעפר נטמן
And was buried in the dust
בכי מר לא יעירו
Bitter crying won't wake him up
לא יחזירו לכאן
And won't bring him back
איש אותנו לא ישיב
Nobody will bring us back
מבור תחתית אפל
From a dead and darkened pit
כאן לא יועילו
Here
לא שמחת הניצחון
Neither the victory cheer
ולא שירי הלל
Nor songs of praise will help
לכן רק שירו שיר לשלום
So just sing a song for peace
אל תלחשו תפילה
Don't whisper a prayer
מוטב תשירו שיר לשלום
Better just sing a song for peace
בצעקה גדולה
In a loud shout
תנו לשמש לחדור
Allow the sun to penetrate
מבעד לפרחים
Through the flowers
אל תביטו לאחור
Don't look back
הניחו להולכים
Let go of those departed
שאו עיניים בתקווה
Lift your eyes with hope
לא דרך כוונות
Not through the rifles' sights
שירו שיר לאהבה
Sing a song for love
ולא למלחמות
And not for wars
אל תגידו יום יבוא
Don't say the day will come
הביאו את היום
Bring on that day
כי לא חלום הוא
Because it is not a dream
ובכל הכיכרות
And in all the city squares
הריעו לשלום
Cheer only for peace
לכן רק שירו שיר לשלום
So just sing a song for peace
אל תלחשו תפילה
Don't whisper a prayer
מוטב תשירו שיר לשלום
Better just sing a song for peace
בצעקה גדולה
In a loud shout
תנו לשמש לעלות
Let the sun rise
לבוקר להאיר
Light up the morning
הזכה שבתפילות
The purest of prayers
אותנו לא תחזיר
Will not bring us back
מי אשר כבה נרו
He whose candle was snuffed out
ובעפר נטמן
And was buried in the dust
בכי מר לא יעירו
Bitter crying won't wake him up
לא יחזירו לכאן
And won't bring him back
לכן רק שירו שיר לשלום
So just sing a song for peace
אל תלחשו תפילה
Don't whisper a prayer
מוטב תשירו שיר לשלום
Better just sing a song for peace
בצעקה גדולה
In a loud shout
שירו שיר לשלום
Sing a song for peace
אל תלחשו תפילה
Don't whisper a prayer
מוטב תשירו שיר לשלום
Better just sing a song for peace
בצעקה גדולה
In a loud shout